scan? These sentences cover the entire scan, from evening to first diagnostic test for all students in consultation with the treatment plant, emergency
ambulance hospital accommodation, post hospitalization for hospitalization and post hospitalization in which you can get cured within 15 days that if you get yourself
treated and it is
party or
intercity, you get castor oil in 30
minutes, we will do
this line meeting these
days for specific diseases you get 24
months and for this you get 1 crore, for example, if you
know about the England team, for example, we have taken 1
crore  It is and we have taken it
now let us
know about one thing so we have taken it as an example there is another one and we have
taken it and
about this Sadhu
28,251 ft
Kaya Abhigyan Shakuntal
know about the team of Spain so the example which I have
taken as per is crore and two adults
we have taken that the age of the relative person is
60 years now let us know about China
so in Nibhana
47600 four
examples we know about this tree
so we have taken it as an example one more
and
now about us
how would you have liked the information about Delhi if you
need any information you can do it with help that's all
for today we will meet
with me in the next video there
is a difference in this video thank you very much
[Music] it has
happened
that a